countryoutfitter.com 2016-11-22

# Privacy Policy | County Outfitter

Thanks for visiting! We want to assure you that your privacy is safe with us at Country Outfitter. This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal information that this site gathers when you access or use our online store. For details, continue reading:

## Information We Collect

The countryoutfitter.com website is operated by Acumen Brands, Inc. Like most websites, countryoutfitter.com collects non-personally identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally-identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use this website. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of this website.

Country Outfitter also collects potentially personally-identifying-information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We do not use such information to identify our visitors, however, and do not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that we use and disclose personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Our Customers - Information You Provide to Us

Certain actions on our website do require us to collect personally-identifying information. Purchasers are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process transactions. In each case, Country Outfitter collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with our company. We will never disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Aggregated Statistics

Country Outfitter may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Country Outfitter may monitor the most popular sections or products on our site. Country Outfitter may display this non-personally-identifying information publicly or provide it to others. However, Country Outfitter does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying-Information

Country Outfitter discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf, or to provide services requested by the customer, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using CountryOutfitter.com, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Country Outfitter will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Country Outfitter discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Country Outfitter, third parties or the public at large. Country Outfitter takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Without cookies, Country Outfitter can't keep track of the items you've placed in your cart or perform other crucial ecommerce capabilities. We do not use cookies to intrude in your privacy or do anything other than match you up with your information on our site.

## Communications

## Email Privacy Policy

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.

## Why did you receive an email from us?

If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

## How we protect your privacy

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of data used by our system.

## Sharing and Usage

We may share the information we collect with our affiliate and subsidiary companies, vendors and their participants, and other third parties, including to inform you about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. We will never sell or rent individual personal information to outside parties without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

## How can you stop receiving email from us?

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email. You can also send the word UNSUBSCRIBE via email to reply@reply.countryoutfitter.com and you will immediately be removed from all related email lists.

If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to info@countryoutfitter.com for review.

## Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit the Country Outfitter website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Arkansas state law.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor and infrequent, Country Outfitter may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Questions

Our full contact information, including location, may be found on our Contact page at [http://countryoutfitter.com/contact.](https://www.countryoutfitter.com/contact)

## Creative Commons

[](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/)This work (the Privacy Policy) is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 2.5 License. (Thanks [toOpenDNS](https://www.opendns.com/privacy-policy/) and [Automattic](https://automattic.com/privacy/) )

## Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 1st, 2008. Last updated August 26th, 2012.
